#### Contact

+85593392690 (Mobile) vorreakboth@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/vorreakboth (LinkedIn)

## **Top Skills**

Integrated Systems
Systems Management
Systems Engineering Process

### Languages

English

Central Khmer

#### **Certifications**

Machine Learning with Python at IBM

Intro to Machine Learning at Kaggle

Python Programming at Kaggle

AWS Cloud Practitioner Essentials

Web Security Essential at SalaCyber

Ethical Hacking Essential at SalaCyber

Cybersecurity Essentials at Cisco

Mobile App Development at CKCC

iOS App Development at CKCC

# Vorreakboth Chhoeurn

System Engineer @ Mobile C&C | Cisco and IBM Certified Phnom Penh, Cambodia

# **Summary**

As a System Engineer at Mobile C&C, I use my bachelor's degree in computer science and my skills in Linux Server, and System to deploy Core Banking System and Bakong System. I have over three years of experience in this role, and previously I worked as Android App Developer, iOS App Developer, and Linux System Administrator, where I gained valuable experience in mobile app development and server management. I am passionate about using technology to solve problems and create value for customers and stakeholders. I enjoy working with a diverse and collaborative team that shares my vision and values. I am always eager to learn new skills and technologies that can help me improve my performance and deliver quality results.

# **Experience**

Mobile C&C (Cambodia) Co.,Ltd.

System Engineer

October 2021 - Present

- Set up, Configure, Troubleshoot and Upgrade Bakong CM System
- Set up, Configure, Troubleshoot and Upgrade RFT CM System
- Set up, Configure, Troubleshoot and Upgrade Fast 2.0 System
- Set up, Configure and Troubleshoot Core Banking System
- Deployed Application to Docker Container
- Set up and Configure Grafana Monitoring System
- Support Daily Operation of Systems

Khonnect

10 months

Wordpress Developer March 2021 - October 2021 (8 months)

- Using Wordpress CMS to build website

#### Linux System Administrator

March 2021 - October 2021 (8 months)

- Deployed web application to Digital Ocean
- Deployed web application to AWS
- Setup TinyCP

#### Web Designer

January 2021 - October 2021 (10 months)

- Design Website using Adobe XD

#### Kasegro Co., Ltd.

1 year 8 months

#### Software Tester

- December 2019 January 2021 (1 year 2 months)
- Manual test the app before publishing new features

# Mobile Application Developer

October 2019 - January 2021 (1 year 4 months)

- Involve to develop eCommerce app
- Fix bugs of the app
- Add new features to the app
- Deployed native app to play store and app store

#### **UX & UI Designer**

June 2019 - October 2019 (5 months)

- Design mobile app using Adobe XD based on the requirement

#### ComeBackApp

6 months

#### Mobile Application Developer

June 2019 - August 2019 (3 months)

- Designed UI and UX for new features
- Implemented User Interface for mobile app
- Deployed native app to play store and app store

#### Software Tester

March 2019 - August 2019 (6 months)

- Manual test the app to find errors

#### Software Localization

March 2019 - August 2019 (6 months)

- Translate string in mobile app
- Add localization to the text for translation

**Best Life Product** 

1 year 2 months

**Technical Trainer** 

October 2018 - March 2019 (6 months)

- Write documentation how to use the app

Train staffs to use the app

- Update the app based on feedback from client

Android Developer

May 2018 - October 2018 (6 months)

- Scan qr-code for login
- Store the records of operation
- Display reports from data that has been recorded

Laravel Developer

May 2018 - October 2018 (6 months)

- Make API for login with qr-code
- Make API for android app to store data
- Make API for android app to display reports

**UX & UI Designer** 

February 2018 - May 2018 (4 months)

- Work with General Manager to know about operation
- Make System Requirements Specification based on operation
- Design UX & UI based on System Requirements Specification

# **Education**

Royal University of Phnom Penh

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science · (2015 - 2019)